Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart
Again, you're running from me
Following you around
is making me lonely
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby
Told me not to love, but I already fell
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well
Baby, I'm crush on ya
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart
Hello there, my darling
If you were a laundry,
I'd be your Rinse Charming
Ready for love,
I have two shoulders for you to lean over,
Even though they feel heavy,
carrying my own beauty (Yep)
I know, I'm just your type, aren't I?
You're so hot like fire (Huh?!)
Because my heart burns for you (Right!)
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
Baby, I wanna tell you something…
I love you!
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart
Besides, I can hear his heartbeats
going, Thump-thump,
thump-thump, so loud and resonating.
Khem!
Jeab, have you been waiting long?
Oh, not at all, Yu-sensei.
So, can I win your heart?
I didn't want to go.
I hated bullies.
Me?
If you stand by and do nothing,
you're one of them, aren't you?
Don't you walk away from me like that.
Just dump someone like him already.
Khem!
Bastard!
If I was being a jerk
or in the wrong,
take it out on me!!
You...
have no fucking right
to lay a finger on my boyfriend!
You've been anxious about Khem, right?
Fu...
Let me kiss you.
Baby, I'm preying on you tonight,
hunt you down, eat you alive.
You sleep like a cute kitty.
Still not awake yet?
Maybe I'll have to double that?
Fu...
don't just talk the talk.
Just lie still, then.
Because I...
will do that work for you.
The favors for the ceremony have all arrived.
It's such an honor...
that you chose our hotel
as your wedding venue, Ms. Lin.
Uh, isn't Mr. Lang,
your groom-to-be, here with you?
They sent staff
to welcome me?
So if you...
Ms. Lin has made
a long trip from Hong Kong.
She needs some rest.
Ms. General Manager, please make sure
there are no disruptions
on the floor where Ms. Lin is staying.
I'll be on it, ma'am.
As for Ms. Lin's personal belongings,
do not touch them.
We'll take care of it.
Alright.
I haven't a clue
what your guest-welcoming standards are,
but in Hong Kong,
with a guest like Ms. Lin,
Mr. Dong Qingshan
should at least welcome her in person.
Please.
If it's that much better,
why aren't they getting married there?
I know, right?
But considering they booked the entire floor,
they must be a big deal.
Jang, please give Ms. Lin
the best possible care.
Thank you.
Is there a problem at the hotel?
It's just a small one,
but Jang can handle it.
Don't worry.
Let's pick up where we left off.
Fu...
Are you sure no one's home?
No one is.
What about Tai and Tee Lek?
They're not home yet.
Waew?
She's gone out.
Right now, we have
this house all to ourselves.
Fu!
Oh!
You two,
you're home already?
What's that shirt you're wearing?
Did some T-Pop idol take over your body?
Just wanna switch up my style.
I've been invested in PERSES lately.
Bodyguard, bodyguard
Moo,
what did you do to my brother?
Uh...
Nothing!!
We... We absolutely didn't
do anything over here at all! Look!
"We didn't do anything..."
Don't tell me
you and Moo were...
Tee!
Stop right there. What are you thinking?
You perv.
There's no way...
Moo and I
were gonna fool around over there!
Jeez, Fu...
Just stop...
Fu!
That's not being slick!
Oh...
I thought you were
gonna cover dance with Moo, though.
I want some alone time with Moo,
but there just have to be spanners in the works.
You damn third wheels!
If you wire me 5,000 baht right now,
I'll take Tai out.
I'll make it 20,000.
Now.
Come on, Tai. Let's go.
- I'm getting so bored with this place.
- What?
Why do you always need so much money?
Are you trying to build a house, huh?
See? That was so close!
- So, so close...
- I even asked you if no one was really going to be home!
Ugh, how was I supposed to know?
Maybe their classes got canceled!
Didn't you say Tee had a tutoring session?
Well, he was supposed to.
Maybe he skipped it?
They're gone.
- They are.
- Tee!
Lin Mingyue
and her fiance
have arrived in Thailand.
Maze,
Mae?
If I had to guess,
they're using a hideout in Thailand
for illegal drug deals, as usual.
I wonder what tricks they’ve
got up their sleeve this time.
A wedding?
Sounds like fun.
I guess
we'll have to congratulate them in person.
Right, Deputy?
We need to plan carefully.
We can't tip them off about it.
- Yes, sir.
Morning, beautiful.
What?
Aren't you going to work?
I was waiting for my intern to wake up.
Fu...
Come on,
let's take a bath.
Then we can head to work together.
I won't get anywhere
if I take a bath with you.
How do you know I won't get you off?
Fu...
Don't say my name so much,
or I'll lose control.
But I'm already so tired...
Come on, I'll take you there.
Let's go take a bath.
Fuu...
Do not test me, Moo-Moo!
Come on, to the bath!
Come here!
No, Fu.
Wait, wait, wait!
Fu!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Of course.
Waew.
Yes?
Anything you'd like to share with us?
Ooh
I...
I wouldn't dare.
Absolutely not.
No way.
Our brother
won't come down for breakfast again?
That's right.
Mr. Fu informed me that
when he woke up,
his breakfast had already been served
right in his bed.
Breakfast in bed...
More like "in bath."
Huh?!
Isn't it gonna make a whole mess?
Why eat in a bathtub?
I'm getting moist!
Argh! Real moist!!
I can't!
I'm flustered.
(Welcome to the wedding of Ling & Lang)
Mae, aren't we blending in too much?
So much...
Very much...
You're not giving off cop energy at all...
Uh...
Let's go. I'm ready.
Hey!
Hello, my name is Jarumas,
or you can call me Jang.
I'm a general manager.
Hello.
Call me Mae.
You may...call me Lucy.
- Ms. Lucy?
- That's right.
Oh, so that must be...
Henry.
Right, Henry.
Right, hello, Ms. Lucy and Mr. Henry.
What a cute couple.
That's ridiculous!
Then, I'd like to take you
to our grand ballroom,
since it's a popular venue for weddings.
Wow, that would be great.
Please, right this way.
Let's toast to Moo.
Cheers.
Alright.
Tian...
What's wrong?
I...
I'm not seeing him anymore.
Who?!
From now on,
I won't get to lie on your shoulder
like this again, will I?
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I don't want you to get in trouble
because of my career path.
And that path
really can't have me in it?
The reason I'm letting you go
is that I love you.
One day,
if I ever get another chance to love you,
I'll take it without hesitation.
I'm not going to promise
that I'll wait for you.
Could it be that someone like me
doesn't deserve to be loved?
Is that it?
Not at all.
Behind the backdrop.
- Right?
- That was suspicious.
Look. Is it right here?
Excuse me.
You were secretly taking photos,
weren't you?
Did you catch any faces or names?
- Ridiculous!
- Not at all.
I'm concerned about a privacy violation.
Oh, right.
- There's nothing of the sort, no!
- None.
It's a beautiful wedding,
so I wanted to take some reference photos.
Mm...
- Right.
- Yes.
Hello,
Mr. Henry
and Ms. Lucy.
My name is Jirat Dong,
but you can call me Fu.
I'm the owner of this hotel.
Oh...
So you're Fu?
Hello there!
Hello.
- Hello, hello.
- Right.
I'm totally in love
with this aesthetic.
May I ask if the hotel organized it?
No, it's not.
It was organized by the client's team.
We just provided the space for rent.
- Oh...
I see.
Here you go, sir.
How much did you put in
for the wedding gift?
Why is there only one?
Jeez, Deputy.
I didn't even give any money.
I just grabbed one.
We have to be more cautious.
Sneaking out evidence like this
can make them suspicious
and tip them off.
Please trust us.
I assure you
our plan will succeed.
I really can trust Henry
and Lucy,
can't I?
Have you also watched '50 First Dates'?
Wow...
Please don't worry, Deputy.
We've made a secret deal with the hotel.
Our plan's gonna
succeed no matter what.
Hello, allow me
to formally introduce myself.
My name is Mae,
and he is Maze.
We are...
police detectives.
We're working on
a transnational drug trafficking case.
We kindly ask that you cooperate, Mr. Fu.
Jang...
Are they real cops?
We are.
- You are. Okay...
- This is not a scam.
So you're saying...
my hotel
is being used by the mafia
to transport drugs?
How could that even be possible?
Well, it is now.
But you can relax.
We'll carry it out as quietly as possible
since this one has powerful backers.
That's how it's supposed to be.
I...
couldn't risk my hotel's reputation
be implicated in such things.
That's right, and the press
can't know anything about it.
Good.
That means that you, you, you,
and the two of us
are all on the same page.
We'll be sure to move very quietly.
We won't damage the hotel's reputation
in the slightest.
I ask that this remain a secret
among everyone in this room.
Regardless, please clear the coast for us.
Let's roll.
Roll where?
Oh...
- To...clear the way...
- The door is right there.
With a ceremony this big,
could it really be kept a secret?
We will do our best.
We will.
You can bet Maze's life on it.
Hey!
What was that about?
Why me?
Whoa, watch out!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Oh...
You work here, too?
Oh, yes.
I'll...
The floor is wet.
Let me wipe it for you first.
Just how many jobs do you do, anyway?
Well...
Thank you
for getting hurt for me.
It's okay.
It's my job anyway.
You still haven't told me
how many jobs you have.
How much do you want to know?
Fine, I don't wanna know.
I'm heading home.
How are you gonna get home?
I'm calling a ride.
(Tai's home)
Hey!
Is this you?
(Your rider, Yu, is ready to pick you up)
Yes.
Then...
I'm going to clock out real quick.
Just wait a moment,
and I'll take you to my car.
Who are you?
We met at the nightclub last night.
Don't you remember?
So why didn't you take me home?
Well, I don't know where you live.
What?
So why didn't you...
take me back to your place?
No way.
You wanted to hook up
the first time we met?
Well...
Sounds pretty normal to me.
I'm not that into you.
Kids,
I'm about to close.
Go home already.
One of you slept like the dead,
while the other stayed up
watching over him all night.
How adorable!
Come on,
- let's go home.
- How cute is that.
Your home, right?
I'm going back to my place.
You head back to yours.
Can't I come with you?
I'm going back to mine,
so go back to yours.
I'd like to apologize to you
for not welcoming you personally.
Finally, we get to meet.
Is everything alright?
Yes, it is.
But the guest and seat numbers
aren't finalized yet.
Lang had me set aside some seats
for special guests.
It would be great if...
I was one of the honored guests
at your wedding
with Mr. Lang.
It would be our honor, too.
Since you said it yourself like this,
how could I not invite you?
In Bangkok,
you seem to have
a wide network of contacts.
You probably have many partners.
The business market in Bangkok
is really big, Ms. Lin.
My partners and I
are always ready to share it with you.
So, I hope that...
the money you put in the box
will be enough to keep us connected.
Ryan.
Young adults are really hot-headed,
aren't they?
Whoa.
You're not with Fu, huh?
He told me
I don't have to intern anymore.
That's strange.
How come?
Maybe the honeymoon phase is over,
like...
he's bored of you or something?
- There you go.
- What?
If my brother hears that,
you're dead meat.
What? That's possible.
Before they started dating,
he was literally obsessed with Moo.
Wanting to see Moo all the time.
But after that,
look,
he distances himself from Moo.
If you ask me,
I think...
something's fishy.
Don't you agree?
Are you gonna keep going?
There's no way
my brother would cheat on Moo.
Believe me.
Right, Moo?
Yeah, he's never going to cheat on me.
I was just warning you.
Please excuse me.
Here is your coffee.
Moo,
why are you here?
I told you that
you didn't have to come, right?
Well...
I used to intern here every day.
I'm not used to
just being gone out of nowhere,
and I haven't said goodbye
to my friends yet.
Isn't that gonna wear you out?
Because tonight,
you also have to fulfill your duty
as my lovely hubby.
Fu!
Don't talk about this stuff at work.
Mmm... Fine.
Tell me.
Why didn't you do as I said?
Well, what are you keeping from me?
Are you just...
jealous of me?
Not at all!
Why do I have to be jealous of you?!
I'm not.
Hmm...
I get excited every time...
you're jealous of me.
Drink your coffee.
No.
I'd rather eat...
you.
Now that you've entered the tiger's den,
you still think you could easily escape,
huh?
"The tiger's den"?
Dame Un Grrr!
My Moo-Moo.
What are you wearing?
Well,
I'm dressing up as your groom, of course.
Because today is...
our wedding day.
Fu!
But today,
you look really handsome.
So Fu-ing handsome.
"So Fu-ing handsome"?
Your intonation is very high.
Maybe you need to relearn the tones.
Oh,
you can head back before me today.
I have to take care of the guests.
I'll see you at home,
alright?
My hubby.
Okay.
Is everything in order?
Yes.
Before they started dating,
he was literally obsessed with Moo.
Wanting to see Moo all the time.
But after that,
look,
he distances himself from Moo.
If you ask me,
I think...
something's fishy.
Thank you to all our Grade-A partners
for coming to my wedding
with Mr. Lang.
Next,
Mr. Lang will give a brief speech
before you sign for
the wedding favors
I hope that after everyone
receives the wedding favors,
you'll continue to support me
so our business can keep growing together.
To mark this new beginning,
I would like
to invite Fu,
the owner of this hotel
and our newest partner,
to come up and give a speech.
Please allow me to introduce myself. I'm Fu,
the owner of Golden Peony Hotel.
First of all,
I'd like to thank
Ms. Lin and Mr. Lang
for giving me this opportunity.
It's indeed a key opportunity.
Thank you so much for trusting me.
Without this,
we won't have a bright future ahead of us.
Without further ado,
shall we sign the contract?
Before we sign the contract...
I would like to ask you one more time.
Are you certain your goods
are as pure as you've guaranteed?
Because if not...
my customers and partners
may be dissatisfied.
What?! How dare you...
Stop.
I'll say it.
To show our sincerity to our partners,
please open
the wedding favors
in your hands.
Inside are
samples of
99.99% pure
meth crystals.
I guarantee
to our guarantors.
You're certainly very confident.
Everything's clear now, yes?
Quality goods, fast shipping, no swindling.
Go ahead, everyone.
"Go ahead, everyone."
Wait, what?
What is this?!
The police have taken control of the situation!
- Mr. Fu!
- Police!
Over here.
Sit down!
What is this?
Sit down! Stop!
Lang!
What the hell is this?!
Miss!
Fu!
Who are you?!
Did they send you?!
Moo!
Fu!
Fu!!
Hey, stop!
Fu!
Fu, you're okay, right?
Fu.
I thought...
I thought I'd never get to say this.
I leth you to dove.
I love you...to death.
Fu! Stay with me, alright?
Open your eyes.
Stay with me, please!
Fu! Fu, do you see me?
I love you, Moo.
I love you too. I love you so, so much.
Fu!
Fu, I love you so much.
Can you hear me? Fu!
Fu, stay with me!
I've always had my eyes on you.
Only you.
Haven't you felt it?
I also want to tell you that
I'll always love you
no matter what.
Fu!
Please stay with me.
Don't leave me!
Fu!
Hey, hey!
- Wait.
- Hey!
Hey, come on. Quickly.
Quick.
Hey, wait!
- Wait!
- Hey!
Hey!
What are you guys doing?!
The teacher's here!
Jirat Dong.
Why don't you act your age and stop doing this?
And look at this. The room's a mess.
You'll clean this room up, alright?
But teacher...
I can't. I have to go home early today.
My parents just came back from overseas.
No buts.
If it's not clean,
you can't go home.
Tai,
tell Papa and Mama to wait for me.
Okay.
That's all.
Moo-Moo?
I didn't do anything!
I just...
I just happened to be passing by.
This is the first day
I'll make you fall for me.
Are you looking for me?
No, I'm just thinking about
whether I should order coffee.
Sheesh!
This room is so damn cool, dude!
As expected of Lady Moo.
It's fitting that my brother has been
madly in love with you for years.
It's Jeab. He's dropping out!
- Huh!?
- Drop out!?
Jeab!
Don't go!
Little Chicken!
Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart
Again, you're running from me
Following you around
is making me lonely
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby
Told me not to love, but I already fell
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well
Baby, I'm crush on ya
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart